<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h3c79d0edg5dfcg0a3cgb5ebg35c5c14223bd" version="1">Alchemist</content>
  <content contentuid="hbab3fe76ge30ag0c5fgbc66g6156ad3c399d" version="1">Infused Reagent</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cb4b477g8a7ag0fd9g7e0fg395fa82e461f" version="1">Versatile Vial</content>
  <content contentuid="h42a0b6f1gf01egbaa6g115agc227faef04d9" version="1">Hide Apron</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c201420g888cg9198g8d5dgbfc22ac3816a" version="1">A thick apron draped over a leather doublet, to protect from the worst of laboratory accidents.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd1beb9ag6e6bgef3fgfdbcg17ae9db51add" version="1">Lob Vial</content>
  <content contentuid="hddf3710bga553g5bcagc44fg787eed052034" version="1">Your versatile vials contain volatile chemicals that can be used offensively in a pinch.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f902c42g38c9gdfe3gdf5agee86a7cd49d4" version="1">AdvancedAlchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="heed6a99eg1179g9d8dg5ed0gcc5f5b932e37" version="2">Brew</content>
  <content contentuid="h65280855g19c9g13aeg9e9bgcb1c18d85f4b" version="1">Infused</content>
  <content contentuid="h39e39d81g0affgc092gbfe8ga8ba8b6c81f3" version="1">An alchemical item with the infused trait has a limited time before it becomes inert. Any non-permanent effects from your infused alchemical items, with the exception of afflictions such as slow-acting poisons, end when you make your daily preparations again. </content>
  <content contentuid="hd4cc6f6fg1448g7cb3g55a1gebbcf5be22a4" version="1">Grease Bottle</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e4b90cdg2a74g9685g3bd7g6ec3c68a5083" version="1">Potion of Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7e57309g85c2gc851g1f5egb6b7e6e6d4c4" version="1">Potion of Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="hf01c7e53ge34eg2e84g743fg760853ba0fe1" version="1">Alchemical Formulas</content>
  <content contentuid="ha9daa1a0g2b23g570ag78c8g9b1e6dbb215d" version="1">An alchemist keeps meticulous formulas for every item they can create. Each time you gain a level, you can add the formulas for two common alchemical items to your formula book.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb139a570g10f7g3f8bg5681gc3cdc6a24c8b" version="1">Versatile Vials</content>
  <content contentuid="hefbbb426gcb7dg4ff3g1c5bg0cf754759818" version="2">Acid Bottle</content>
  <content contentuid="h86a01fefg4645gd9a4gfd3eg0006ab9929b3" version="1">Alchemist's Fire</content>
  <content contentuid="h88ab421bg8b81g0f63g6c06g850aad47def5" version="1">Amulet Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h593c4df3g7aa4ged2cg6aefg5c2b7764d557" version="1">The protective aspects of your amulet can shield you and your allies from harm. You gain the Amulet's Abeyance reaction.&lt;br&gt;Reaction&lt;br&gt;Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability would damage you or an ally within 15 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;You forcefully present your amulet to turn away harm. You or a target ally within 15 feet gain resistance to all damage against the triggering damage. The resistance is equal to 2 + your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e54f499g0497g3239g8478g7561974297d6" version="1">Bell Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h7dcbb14fgecfeg40eage48cg8f6d28ae8107" version="1">You can use your bell implement to create three different kinds of music, each of which weakens a foe in a different way. You gain the Ring Bell activity.&lt;br&gt;Reaction&lt;br&gt;Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Your implement sings out abruptly, disrupting your foe. The piece played depends on whether the trigger was a Strike or Spell, and it applies to the triggering Strike or Spell, except where noted otherwise.&lt;br&gt;Distracting Cacophony The trigger is a spell. You create a musical crash of sonic energy that assails the target and breaks its concentration. The target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become stupefied 1 until the end of your next turn (stupefied 2 on a critical failure). The target doesn't have to attempt a flat check to avoid losing the triggering spell, but the discordant ring does lower the spell attack roll or spell DC of the triggering spell from stupefied.&lt;br&gt;Disrupting Harmony The trigger is a Strike. You create a strangely discordant harmony that sinks into your foe's mind and throws its movements off. The target must succeed at a Will save against your class DC or become your choice of enfeebled 1 or clumsy 1 until the end of your next turn (enfeebled 2 or clumsy 2 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c5bd35dg88c1g727eg9443ga3899e85e3fc" version="1">Chalice Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3fd7d80g3d5cgf01eg12f1ge85b0ff1bf8e" version="1">While holding your chalice, you can drink from it or feed its liquid to an ally to improve their health. You gain the Drink from the Chalice action.&lt;br&gt;1 Action&lt;br&gt;Frequency once per round&lt;br&gt;You drink from the liquid that slowly collects in your chalice or administer it to an adjacent ally. The drinker chooses whether to take a small sip or to drain the contents.&lt;br&gt;Sip A sip grants the drinker an amount of temporary Hit Points equal to 2 + half your level that last until the end of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;Drain (healing, positive) Drinking deep instead heals the drinker 3 Hit Points for each level you have. After the chalice is drained, it's left with only its slowly collecting dregs; the chalice can't be drained again, though it can still be sipped from. If 10 minutes pass without anyone drinking from the chalice, it refills itself and can be drained again. If the drinker has negative healing, it can still heal in this way, and the effect has the negative trait instead of healing and positive.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd80047ceg793bg34edg329eg3352fe0e5e12" version="1">Lantern Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h07605eddg378dg4339g1128g5c0123cc33b1" version="1">While you hold your lantern, its burning light leaves secrets no place to hide. You can light or extinguish your lantern as a free action once each turn with nothing but a thought, which has the concentrate trait. The lantern shines bright light out to 20 feet and dim light out 20 feet further; this has the evocation, light, and magical traits (the counteract level against magical darkness is equal to half your level rounded up).&lt;br&gt;The lantern's magical light attempts to reveal the unseen. You and your allies in the lantern's area of bright light gain a +1 status bonus to visual Perception checks to notice anything that is also within the bright light</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5dfe865gcb7eg397fg777bg785a4e3d1cf8" version="1">Mirror Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h7140187agf431g523fge2f0gf1fd32fc1d68" version="1">You learn how to use your mirror to project another version of yourself whose realness is a matter of perspective. You gain the Mirror's Reflection action.&lt;br&gt;1 Action&lt;br&gt;You reflect an illusory image of yourself into another unoccupied space within 15 feet that you can see. You are treated as being in both spaces until the start of your next turn. For example, you can attack, Seek, and provide flanking—even with yourself. You occupy both spaces.&lt;br&gt;Some events force you to determine which image is the real you, and then end the effect and cause your mirror self to disappear; this happens automatically at the start of your next turn. It also happens if you choose to move out of your space. Other benefits of this implement add more events that can end the reflection. The effect also ends when you fall unconscious, at which point you decide which version is truly you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h29a8985bg396cg3f90g849dg8324c42a2b95" version="1">Regalia Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h429aae9fgb71eg4791g62d0g5f0e83f85958" version="1">While you hold your regalia, you gain an air of authority and bolster the courage of allies who believe in you. Your regalia aids you when you attempt to convince others. You gain a +1 circumstance bonus to Deception, Diplomacy, and Intimidation checks.&lt;br&gt;When you are holding your regalia, you gain an inspiring aura that stokes the courage of you and all allies in a 15-foot emanation who can see you, granting them a +1 status bonus to saving throws against fear. At the end of your turn, at the same time you would reduce your frightened value by 1, you reduce the frightened value of all allies within your inspiring aura by 1. Your aura has the emotion, mental, and visual traits.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0962f74g9c72g6b52g0c6fg58353ee0ad33" version="1">Tome Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f7e3a02gf7d0gea5cgb476g48f2ad099157" version="1">You are trained in two additional skills. You gain an additional skill increase at level 3 and 5.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf080ff16gecc6gcb1ag3511g10c69104740d" version="2">Wand Initiate (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="h13eb29a4gebe9gbb17g7c86g12dc0af0b470" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb3103de6gf1c2g1151gf3fbgd3ab6cf4c38a" version="1">Weapon Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8f50018g080cg8d05g2a05g3aaa92faa79c" version="1">Your weapon trembles slightly in your hand, seeking out your foe's weakness to it and interrupting their actions. You gain the Attack of Opportunity reaction.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3520d26egb29fg646bgc6b0gf179fc5a7e8c" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h1db061f4gadb4g61d3g3a89gd41148e273e2" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb01de7eg3a4cgfd2bg9fc1g11b2eb84fa5d" version="1">Bell Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hc29b0c6fgbaeeg7de1g4221g4476a9a600f2" version="1">Your bell resonates powerfully, causing the effect to last longer. The conditions from Ring Bell last 3 rounds instead of 1 round.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e16c3a9ge236g691dga5c1gc1c7921e9366" version="1">Chalice Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h1038ab67g5159gb55ag5155g010c812fbf1c" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3aef4bfbg0b0fge11bg462bg6ed9926d8e7a" version="1">Lantern Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h4288af42g92f8g536cg1e93g29ddab2abb62" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, when you hold your lantern, its light reveals the invisible and the ethereal. The bright light increases to 30 feet, with dim light out 30 feet further. While you're holding your lantern, invisible and ethereal creatures within the bright light become visible as rippling distortions, though they're still concealed. This doesn't give you any special ability to affect a creature on the Ethereal Plane, but it ensures you're aware of the creatures' presence.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a74d471g4dd2g1393gdc34gea5421d27d3f" version="1">Mirror Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb509b4ag1aa8gb599gaed5g8f4291e72949" version="1">Your mirror self shatters into punishing shards when damaged. While Mirror's Reflection is in effect, when an enemy adjacent to one of your spaces damages you, that version of you explodes into mirror shards. This ends Mirror's Reflection (establishing the remaining version of you as the real one) and deals slashing damage to all creatures in a 5-foot emanation around where your mirror self was. The damage is equal to 2 + half your level or the damage of the triggering attack, whichever is lower. You're immune to this damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b41c3d5g7a5age7dbg48ceg32f0cc912db8" version="1">Regalia Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hf80291e1gb313gb2d4g01e3g3d171d914033" version="1">Your regalia's power increases, and so do the abilities it grants. The circumstance bonus you gain to Deception, Diplomacy, and Intimidation increases to +2&lt;br&gt;The courage your aura instills grows stronger. The +1 status bonus now applies to all saving throws against mental effects, rather than only against fear, and you and allies in your aura gain a +2 status bonus to damage rolls. At 11th level, this increases to a +3 status bonus to damage rolls, and at 17th level, this increases to a +4 status bonus to damage rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3e540c75g488fgd2c1g49e9gc580ba9f6e74" version="1">Tome Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5dd6ce7ga693g1578g505cgc1dd4e31e073" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, your tome inscribes insights into creatures that you can use to strike them down. While holding your tome, at the start of your turn each round, attempt a check to Recall Knowledge about a creature of your choice that you're observing. If this check succeeds, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack roll against that creature before the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5673120bg062fgcce5g2ae8g60ac9fd7af0b" version="1">Wand Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h013df7e6gaa66gc186g2dbagfe3e3f064788" version="1">You gain versatility and additional benefits when you fire your wand. The range of Fling Magic increases to 120 feet. Choose a second damage type from the list; whenever you Fling Magic, you can select between either of the two damage types you have chosen. Fling Magic has an additional effect if the target fails its save and takes damage, depending on the type.&lt;br&gt;Cold: The target becomes chilled, taking a –10-foot status penalty to its Speeds for 1 round.&lt;br&gt;Electricity: The target is shocked, becoming flat-footed until the end of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;Fire: The target catches flame, taking 1d10 persistent fire damage (or 2d10 on a critical failure). If you have the wand paragon benefit, this increases to 2d10 persistent fire damage (or 4d10 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h2835ecbbg6c4ag4813g6e69g96b4131d3636" version="1">Weapon Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h0defc74cgf372g901ag3a6fg791eac0effab" version="1">When your implement lashes out at your foe, even a close miss brings the weapon close enough to do harm. When you use Implement's Interruption and fail (but don't critically fail) the Strike, you deal 1 damage of the weapon's normal type, possibly applying any bonus damage due to the target's weakness.</content>
  <content contentuid="h618c5809g150bg1e04gf1f0g1ab3aa5fff8a" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Amulet)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd96118bcgb6fega3c5g3af5geb9224a1c0b2" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbadc67f6ga101g7504g40b8ge35d0a2d97b7" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Bell)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3f9e82efg62ecgb5c7gb51fg721a18688ac9" version="2">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h2845aa39g3d6cg0e25gbfc2gf306031d49e3" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Chalice)</content>
  <content contentuid="h68f3be88g85aeg1ae9g6eabgca8cd2b54562" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf6c8ed5cgfb94gf62eg9f4bg4637d98fa23e" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Lantern)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ee1d37dgdaf5g564dga881g79d6fbe6a076" version="1">Your lantern's light flares and burns bright, leaving no shadows in which secrets and enemies can hide. Against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, the status bonuses from the lantern's initiate benefit increase to +2. The creature takes a –2 status penalty to Deception checks and Stealth checks as long as it's within the lantern's light. The creature can't be concealed while it's in the lantern's light, though it still can potentially become hidden or undetected using cover or means other than the concealed condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6229f5e2g6b39ge76bgb8f3g9a43cc4aa419" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Mirror)</content>
  <content contentuid="h7507c882g1498gb5b7g970dgef4eb08c8b96" version="1">Reinforcing your mirror lets it play tricks on your enemy's senses as it bends light this way or that. You become concealed to the target of your Exploit Vulnerability as your mirror warps its perceptions. As normal for concealment where your overall location is still obvious, you can't use this concealment to Hide or Sneak.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa709951g1815g8bcag2feag8d1bf28783a2" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Regalia)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bdfdf00gfa00g1340gee3bgf45789049271" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, choose an ally that you can see. That ally gains a +1 circumstance bonus to its attack rolls against the creature until the beginning of your next turn. If the attack roll was a critical hit, the circumstance bonus increases to +2.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d9c3a35geef1gd866g9a10gc452db2e4485" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Tome)</content>
  <content contentuid="h11ca9522g6c6dgfb05g32f6gceb1c105eee1" version="1">Your tome's power not only reads a creature's present but even records its future actions. When you use Intensify Vulnerability, roll a d20 and set the result aside. At any time until the start of your next turn, you can use the d20 result you set aside for an attack roll to Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, instead of rolling a new d20; this is a fortune effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8528da86g0ac0g8aa8ge6ffg43e3788d58ac" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Wand)</content>
  <content contentuid="h01219aa1gb83dg9628g6e30g0cbf7d079482" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8dbfe23g70d5gcff6gaac1g7136b85e2868" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Weapon)</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c9e784dg51c9g3a62g48c2g882d8a78aacc" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h71d606f4g89f5g19e9g76cag6534ff62eeb4" version="1">Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hfe7512e8g0687g0cc1ga3a7gc0b0be80822d" version="1">Amulets are items carried for good luck and protection. Your amulet might be a magical diagram, a religious symbol, a preserved body part such as a rabbit's foot, or a lucky coin. Amulet implements are associated with the harrow suit of shields and the astrological signs of the bridge and the ogre.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ba7d30cgab75gc188g8b95g202987364b5a" version="1">Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="ha6c50cd4g82e0gcf60g683agadcb9c618505" version="1">Bells symbolize the power that sounds and emotions hold over others, soothing with one tone and startling with another. Bells, drums, finger cymbals, and other percussion instruments are most typical, but these implements can be any type of portable musical instrument that is played with one hand. Bell implements are associated with the astrological signs of the daughter and the blossom.</content>
  <content contentuid="hefa4ffb6g0ea5g465ag3bcfgda737d67011e" version="1">Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1ae0f6fg289eg6520g6e1ag7c5965f8e3a1" version="1">Chalice implements are vessels that fill with liquid, associating them with healing, nourishment, and life. Your chalice might be a traditional cup or goblet, but it could also be a small amphora, a polished gourd, or even a hollowed-out skull. Chalice implements are associated with the astrological signs of the mother and the newlyweds, as well as the sea dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h192bd302g612ega04bg4541g3bba0576c92f" version="1">Lantern</content>
  <content contentuid="h2250ef7cgd86dgcb57g6168g97eab744149d" version="1">Lantern implements shine the light of revelation to part shadows and expose truth. You might use a common glass lantern, torch, paper lantern, or other similar light source. Lantern implements are associated with the harrow suit of stars and the astrological signs of the lantern bearer and the archer.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2816a95gc94ag1e44g7b0cg484d3c318558" version="1">Mirror</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd3ef137g59e7ga3b8gfc48g7e240da2f839" version="1">Mirror implements represent misdirection, illusion, and sleight of hand, bending and shifting a perspective and the way you look at things. While larger mirrors hold the same mystic connotations, thaumaturges always choose small, portable, handheld mirrors as implements so they can use them easily while adventuring. Mirror implements are associated with the harrow suit of keys, and the astrological signs of the stranger and the swallow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h48ea037dg7dbdg9ed5g8700g7f54a77c724a" version="1">Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e5691e9ge107gbbafg3f83g92259918cdc7" version="1">Regalia implements represent rulership, leadership, and social connections. While they differ in shape depending on regional customs and markers used to signify authority, common regalia implements are scepters, jeweled orbs, and heraldic banners. Regalia implements are associated with the harrow suit of crowns and the astrological signs of the patriarch and the sovereign dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfa0ef68gb400g54fdg50f8g789cfdf4db47" version="1">Tome</content>
  <content contentuid="h61de0bd1g3521ga3c7g9009g6672ad351096" version="1">Tome implements embody lost knowledge and otherworldly insights. While a weathered book is most common, tome implements can have as many different form factors as there are ways to store knowledge, from carved clay tablets to bundles of knotted cords. Tome implements are associated with the harrow suit of books and the astrological signs of the stargazer and the underworld dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h83a6a6abga6dcgd64eg9a66gb6d31bc49e86" version="1">Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h5526d369g32bbg4977g3271g12e38ca67470" version="1">Wand implements are short, lightweight batons, usually made of wood but often incorporating other materials. Due to their association with spellcasters, wand implements are connected to magic and its practice, as well as the direction and manipulation of energy. Wand implements are associated with the astrological signs of the thrush and the sky dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f389ea5g6dd2g11a8gfb49g25c87ddd647d" version="1">Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1cbbf97ga21cge43fgb1ddg972f0aaf2b43" version="1">Weapon implements are the most direct and confrontational, representing battle, struggle, and potentially violence. You can choose only a one-handed weapon as an implement, which allows you to channel energies into your weapon as well as hold your other implements once you gain them. Weapon implements are associated with the harrow suit of hammers and the astrological signs of the rider and the swordswoman.</content>
  <content contentuid="h803bf079g9cc5g70efg3282g3b3f5a1c936d" version="1">Thaumaturge</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f570512gecb6gbe0eg6660gdccc7ccbcf12" version="1">The thaumaturge has seen every monster and knows every secret. Supplementing their skill at arms and ability to strike a monster’s weakness with myriad supernatural trinkets and mystic implements that can fill a wide range of roles, the thaumaturge is a versatile agent who can contribute to any team facing the unknown.</content>
  <content contentuid="h205bb61dg5441g3a8eg28d8g394fe1f92a93" version="1">Amulet Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h84564481g9f53g9a80gca82gf37eb49c3483" version="1">Amulets are items carried for good luck and protection. Your amulet might be a magical diagram, a religious symbol, a preserved body part such as a rabbit's foot, or a lucky coin. Amulet implements are associated with the harrow suit of shields and the astrological signs of the bridge and the ogre.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha940f463gb254g53d0g4695g603acb8a5461" version="1">Bell Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h835a6870g8306g1b8fgc2a5gdcfa787ff4a3" version="1">Bells symbolize the power that sounds and emotions hold over others, soothing with one tone and startling with another. Bells, drums, finger cymbals, and other percussion instruments are most typical, but these implements can be any type of portable musical instrument that is played with one hand. Bell implements are associated with the astrological signs of the daughter and the blossom.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0130b7eg773fga704g9fb4gefb0d08ed3f7" version="1">Chalice Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h4843ac2eg0067gff21ga579gd9adc7a3a614" version="1">Chalice implements are vessels that fill with liquid, associating them with healing, nourishment, and life. Your chalice might be a traditional cup or goblet, but it could also be a small amphora, a polished gourd, or even a hollowed-out skull. Chalice implements are associated with the astrological signs of the mother and the newlyweds, as well as the sea dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d886b3egc3fbg037bg2e58g6cc9d82b8531" version="1">Lantern Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="haa0dd64dg6dfdg9088g773bg279f73ef030c" version="1">Lantern implements shine the light of revelation to part shadows and expose truth. You might use a common glass lantern, torch, paper lantern, or other similar light source. Lantern implements are associated with the harrow suit of stars and the astrological signs of the lantern bearer and the archer.</content>
  <content contentuid="he625da99g6d39gcc1cg75f1g36b609113678" version="1">Mirror Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h445facc0g14a3g58afg6e30g2d044439b40c" version="1">Mirror implements represent misdirection, illusion, and sleight of hand, bending and shifting a perspective and the way you look at things. While larger mirrors hold the same mystic connotations, thaumaturges always choose small, portable, handheld mirrors as implements so they can use them easily while adventuring. Mirror implements are associated with the harrow suit of keys, and the astrological signs of the stranger and the swallow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b580a88gcb14gc105g02c8g98260694fde8" version="1">Regalia Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h97db613fg1987gc20cg3662ga24b79004d6c" version="1">Regalia implements represent rulership, leadership, and social connections. While they differ in shape depending on regional customs and markers used to signify authority, common regalia implements are scepters, jeweled orbs, and heraldic banners. Regalia implements are associated with the harrow suit of crowns and the astrological signs of the patriarch and the sovereign dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfa6ed9cg565ag7f78g491fg1dea4309f030" version="1">Tome Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h18bfc33dg29a3g2901g89b2g4d333b4522ae" version="1">Tome implements embody lost knowledge and otherworldly insights. While a weathered book is most common, tome implements can have as many different form factors as there are ways to store knowledge, from carved clay tablets to bundles of knotted cords. Tome implements are associated with the harrow suit of books and the astrological signs of the stargazer and the underworld dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2a6da91gb864ge572g78cdg590ec20f148e" version="1">Wand Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d891c49g4373g5048g7ecegfb0ddb0acd64" version="1">Wand implements are short, lightweight batons, usually made of wood but often incorporating other materials. Due to their association with spellcasters, wand implements are connected to magic and its practice, as well as the direction and manipulation of energy. Wand implements are associated with the astrological signs of the thrush and the sky dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hde11f54dga8d9g4e01g0a31g173aea80963c" version="1">Weapon Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h47765644geee6g5740g2e5fgb4639ed1b487" version="1">Weapon implements are the most direct and confrontational, representing battle, struggle, and potentially violence. You can choose only a one-handed weapon as an implement, which allows you to channel energies into your weapon as well as hold your other implements once you gain them. Weapon implements are associated with the harrow suit of hammers and the astrological signs of the rider and the swordswoman.</content>
  <content contentuid="h793767ecg0ae9g049cg69f6g5055d6b4e729" version="1">Exploit Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="h714678b6g8195gde70g8094g9fd72c08c669" version="1">1 Action &lt;br&gt;Personal Antithesis You improvise a custom weakness on a creature by forcefully presenting and empowering a piece of esoterica that repels it on an individual level; for instance, against a tyrant, you might procure a broken chain that once held a captive. This causes the target creature, and only the target creature, to gain a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21fcea3fg7232g2ac3g0bf7gea0fc3ee32ff" version="1">Implement's Empowerment</content>
  <content contentuid="h54bfbeabg192dg55bbg6950gaf77e43e22e3" version="1">The power of your implement can also be turned to the more common task of combat, its power adding to and amplifying the effects of runes and other magical empowerments. When you Strike, you can trace mystic patterns with an implement you're holding to empower the Strike, causing it to deal 2 additional damage per weapon damage die. Channeling the power requires full use of your hands. You don't gain the benefit of implement's empowerment if you are holding anything in either hand other than a single one-handed weapon, other implements, or esoterica, and you must be holding at least one implement to gain the benefit.&lt;br&gt;This is automatic and is +2 at level 1, +4 at level 4, and +6 at level 12.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ca3579bg7d30g4eb6g54eagab2e390e9489" version="1">Select Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h675a1dd0geaa0g598bg1e68g5799300d0bc2" version="1">Exploited Bonuses</content>
  <content contentuid="h261bac52g67b7g7056gfc50g37ea68fa38d1" version="1">You designate a single creature to gain a weakness to you weapon and unarmed attacks equal to [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h8076ca22g8cfag69c2ga8f8g29524832b4e1" version="1">Exploit Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="h2bb6f450g9438gf0d8gbf1bg0576f09d604c" version="1">Personal Antithesis You improvise a custom weakness on a creature by forcefully presenting and empowering a piece of esoterica that repels it on an individual level; for instance, against a tyrant, you might procure a broken chain that once held a captive. This causes the target creature, and only the target creature, to gain a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb9198c4g5cedg1a4dga804gd199e34d4bbd" version="1">Exploited</content>
  <content contentuid="h61ae3b9eg1343g6615g819eg37742c48d0e0" version="1">Affected entity has a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h03cbb709gacb0g17fcg8c91gaf572ae68981" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4f130cbg415eg1b55g3954gd9e56d1997cb" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="h608b50a7gbc5fgaa1ag353agb8a00afa8872" version="1">Sip A sip grants the drinker an amount of temporary Hit Points equal to 2 + half your level that last until the end of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd8d03dagc8f0gc5d0gf555gedcaab0fe0e7" version="1">Chalice (Drain)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9512c78g49bdgf81bg8916g878593852f52" version="1">Drain (healing, positive) Drinking deep instead heals the drinker 3 Hit Points for each level you have. After the chalice is drained, it's left with only its slowly collecting dregs; the chalice can't be drained again, though it can still be sipped from. If 10 minutes pass without anyone drinking from the chalice, it refills itself and can be drained again. If the drinker has negative healing, it can still heal in this way, and the effect has the negative trait instead of healing and positive.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3b274a3g760eg38e0gefe0g5ccc12e5f4d2" version="1">Lantern (Light)</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ef6ef2eg88fagb982g5073gc43788f17922" version="1">While you hold your lantern, its burning light leaves secrets no place to hide. You can light or extinguish your lantern as a free action once each turn with nothing but a thought, which has the concentrate trait. The lantern shines bright light out to 20 feet and dim light out 20 feet further; this has the evocation, light, and magical traits (the counteract level against magical darkness is equal to half your level rounded up).</content>
  <content contentuid="h77c4c1ddga7fbgfe9bg636age30fd69d9e19" version="1">Mirror's Reflection</content>
  <content contentuid="h83cea158g7511g4598gdef3g7a2b9b40c5d3" version="1">1 Action&lt;br&gt; You reflect an illusory image of yourself into another unoccupied space within 15 feet that you can see. You are treated as being in both spaces until the start of your next turn. For example, you can attack, Seek, and provide flanking—even with yourself. You occupy both spaces.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfd27d6fg99aag29cdg31degfedd49550e3e" version="1">Amulet's Abeyance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e2eea1egfa25g9dccg7bd2g70f784817fb8" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability would damage you or an ally within 15 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You're holding your amulet implement and are benefiting from Exploit Vulnerability.&lt;br&gt;You forcefully present your amulet to turn away harm. You or a target ally within 15 feet gain resistance to all damage against the triggering damage. The resistance is equal to 2 + your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3ba6944gfcebg704ag1db5gf22525215768" version="1">Ring Bell (Spell)</content>
  <content contentuid="h43e7ef5fg5ca4g5269gcab6g15e504eda14a" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Distracting Cacophony The trigger is a spell. You create a musical crash of sonic energy that assails the target and breaks its concentration. The target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become stupefied 1 until the end of your next turn (stupefied 2 on a critical failure). The target doesn't have to attempt a flat check to avoid losing the triggering spell, but the discordant ring does lower the spell attack roll or spell DC of the triggering spell from stupefied.</content>
  <content contentuid="h142c8950g9dc6gb1c6g329dge6887a8a1e5e" version="1">Ring Bell (Strike)</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb6676f2g2bbdg975fgc7fbg4f9ad3d06d22" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Disrupting Harmony The trigger is a Strike. You create a strangely discordant harmony that sinks into your foe's mind and throws its movements off. The target must succeed at a Will save against your class DC or become your choice of enfeebled 1 or clumsy 1 until the end of your next turn (enfeebled 2 or clumsy 2 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h726d7604g8dcbg44c2g0d5cg67935cb0abfe" version="1">Mirror (Swap)</content>
  <content contentuid="h63e353f5gd62bga11dg671cgc1c280b4c23f" version="1">Swap places with a mirror duplicate.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd432f4c7ge156gd430g2aaag74bde4911892" version="5">Illusory Double</content>
  <content contentuid="h23bd51e3geabegab25g2b38g0dbee8222c6d" version="1">Fling Magic (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="he8e089f0ge24agf10dg43e4g0bc245ccc833" version="1">You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.</content>
  <content contentuid="hab17ebbdgca3cg6e26g3944gfefc377b88d9" version="1">Fling Magic (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="h71fe5accg1c62g9a2bg36cbg946c0c464774" version="1">Fling Magic (Electricity)</content>
  <content contentuid="h51e8a5bfg0670g4627g8bafg21d5ec1caadc" version="1">Fling Magic (Cold) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="hff2d2db3g91c6geaa5gff06g2a7a4f1cb9d3" version="1">Fling Magic (Fire) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="h534c6a5egeb66gbafege0b0g399c6d883b3c" version="1">Fling Magic (Electricity) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="h59272a07g2778gbe27g36f4g50854674b918" version="1">Regalia Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a4bdc84gd9cagd7f0gead7g8b61699e3436" version="1">The courage your aura instills grows stronger. The +1 status bonus now applies to all saving throws against mental effects, rather than only against fear, and you and allies in your aura gain a +2 status bonus to damage rolls. At 11th level, this increases to a +3 status bonus to damage rolls, and at 17th level, this increases to a +4 status bonus to damage rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb93f9874ge2aag7dc5gcc8fg9c6a1fe36fe5" version="1">Intensify Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="h14e56a07gaf19g4ca7gabb1g589554c082ff" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd08b3e8ag25b1g5509g281cg9f6c7dd9f98e" version="1">Intensify Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="h02759b57g8856g2888g53cfg0769d04d468f" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b52e905geec6g6a77g48d4gb3149f7c0e83" version="1">Intensify Mirror</content>
  <content contentuid="hebed587cgf00bga809g2c65g80dbc580c1ca" version="1">Reinforcing your mirror lets it play tricks on your enemy's senses as it bends light this way or that. You become concealed to the target of your Exploit Vulnerability as your mirror warps its perceptions. As normal for concealment where your overall location is still obvious, you can't use this concealment to Hide or Sneak.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bfcca8dg1a8fgfe15ge9c9g60385c54a63d" version="1">Intensify Tome</content>
  <content contentuid="hbecf337eg7a58g94c3g9969g44197262457a" version="1">Your tome's power not only reads a creature's present but even records its future actions. When you use Intensify Vulnerability, roll a d20 and set the result aside. At any time until the start of your next turn, you can use the d20 result you set aside for an attack roll to Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, instead of rolling a new d20; this is a fortune effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbac6351cg3554g14e1ga437gc3ae38448f38" version="1">Intensify Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h679cf409g4c4dg6b1ag28eeg510bdbee1108" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="h26bb7652gb6e4g00a6g35e3gde86756a03c9" version="1">Intensify Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cabd202g40c2gf010g2f67g5a463e7c3a07" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="he0b003f7gb16egd518g31b2g342613c3a7c9" version="1">Tome Recall</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e304826gaa3dgb03cg2791ge29ffce75976" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, your tome inscribes insights into creatures that you can use to strike them down. While holding your tome, at the start of your turn each round, attempt a check to Recall Knowledge about a creature of your choice that you're observing. If this check succeeds, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack roll against that creature before the start of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;BG3: Persuasion versus Perception.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb831a78cge18cgb458gf9b0gc350bc53105e" version="1">Intensify Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd3d65edg7207g3baag9d01g9c38101e532f" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round, or a –3 status penalty on a critical hit. This effect has the auditory, emotion, and mental traits.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61d96a5bge233g4d82g73adgfd84d4acd2dd" version="1">Intensify Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h40dd9b0bg53dag35fdg3b2fg66714453ea8d" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, choose an ally that you can see. That ally gains a +1 circumstance bonus to its attack rolls against the creature until the beginning of your next turn. If the attack roll was a critical hit, the circumstance bonus increases to +2.</content>
  <content contentuid="he483ea5fg74f7g969eg6b12geea630c27dac" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h7becaf7agebf8g7443ge065gda2954348420" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21fb36b6gf4aagc052g2083ge4d76e74b6c2" version="1">Chalice Adept Bonus</content>
  <content contentuid="hb4da3524g52fdg8f08gba7agf2c93fce88f5" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81f45380gaafbg3d9eg791ag86c8f49dd5bf" version="1">Mirror Shatter</content>
  <content contentuid="h38724484g4911ge171geb2dg02b82cb94401" version="1">Your mirror self shatters into punishing shards when damaged. While Mirror's Reflection is in effect, when an enemy adjacent to one of your spaces damages you, that version of you explodes into mirror shards. This ends Mirror's Reflection (establishing the remaining version of you as the real one) and deals slashing damage to all creatures in a 5-foot emanation around where your mirror self was. The damage is equal to 2 + half your level or the damage of the triggering attack, whichever is lower. You're immune to this damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc444ed28g7851ge07eg2352g003e0a755c5b" version="1">Intensify Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h74a753dbg36d7g20f6gd969g4dc15d027735" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eb5dd3eg6574g5e17g2699g1e19589e2d7b" version="1">Intensify Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="h47be1468g8a6egd172g0f83g138fc170d828" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c2ccc6eg1cbegc434g392eg0252668d669e" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="h792ba08dgfe32g9c83g9c4bg9704fb7b3453" version="1">Portent Dice</content>
  <content contentuid="h6200122egfb98g1630g4ef4ga182089f5c8c" version="1">Affected entity possesses the power to influence the future through divination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entity can use a reaction to change the die of any &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; rolled nearby to a [1].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="h326c2d20gc8edg9307g2dd5ge1483c265664" version="1">Intensified Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="h668a34e5gbec9gbedege67dgdf2d56fe4579" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h59e123a1g3dbeg9791g39acge1d81b460810" version="1">Intensified Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="h00192464g6d40gb912g576dg2e7f613d9129" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h320cfa58gd4e5g9398g6c74gd6d1696d3b82" version="1">Intensified Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="hd4beefc2g491cg3f6cgb36dg327975edd560" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb285973dg450cg0f87gf020ga13d472390fb" version="1">Intensified Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="hee7ebce2g9119g3fe6g378eg4dfed22925c4" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4e8a22cg60e2g09e0g8159gd62f8fa14aa8" version="1">Intensified Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h9bf7d36ag6db1gf05fg475bg184d9bca1161" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a5d9119g94e4g5549g309fgf5c950e42bb0" version="1">Intensified Bell (Debuff)</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ef08f99g07b9geb6fg3dcdg630782490a16" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="he6611890g7337g6eddge888g9124f8206756" version="1">Intensified Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="h424c3bd6g4ffcg2722gb529gff90c8f13625" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h45422406gcca1gb873g1abcgacf4c0caef67" version="1">Bellstruck</content>
  <content contentuid="h76fc9edbg646bg13d6g3c38g0675df3ed691" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="hf93978beg2161gc488gcdc3g52b1953ca972" version="1">Portent Die: 1</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b7c80d0g83b8gd333g986eg2ba0245f4dbb" version="1">Change the die of a nearby &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; to [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h1c1d934bgb383gf88cg0333g749a6e55ec7d" version="1">Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="h848ad874ga30dgb17bg41ddg34944e3114a8" version="1">Wand Initiate (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3365451g0333gd9fbga6e4gf60565ddcbb5" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27052479g325cgbf7cg9203ge1166f15e9d3" version="1">Wand Initiate (Electricity)</content>
  <content contentuid="h9887bb46ge295g6053gb537gb5fa3b3321ff" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a6f32d4g651bgb84dg72e0g14d2f248820e" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3809f698gcd96gb73bg1a88gc61556f72743" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h87910704gfef2gb3f5gbff3g5be85cb68b0b" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h86f29909g9d4agca52gf7fcgcd93c4a47c2f" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h52946b3fga634gbfefg8eb0gbec00b09301c" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a8a3b83gba23gf21fgb6fcge76f03111999" version="1">Exploited</content>
  <content contentuid="h51a54bd4g51dag1a84gb8c5g9b7a67b3828d" version="1">Affected entity has a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcffaf29cg394dgde39g0c60g257ed7603575" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="h49f32135gb505g1da9g2da6g2c35464793a9" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1a40027gf050g208dgda70g57b8907a4ebb" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd3ee20cg03d6g7cc2g14e3gaa2209049825" version="1">Chalice Adept Bonus</content>
  <content contentuid="h3818fc1dg9153g8545g1101gd5e74794e967" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf7db0c64g024egb110ge4a1g3ef615aa4275" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4841586g0e57g4cf3g8408g2b5b335f2599" version="1">Portent Dice</content>
  <content contentuid="h054c6f37ga984g2a72g3459gb9a6fb18f3a7" version="1">Affected entity possesses the power to influence the future through divination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entity can use a reaction to change the die of any &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; rolled nearby to a [1].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="heb79ed83gac02ga389ga2cbg79c10d634fc1" version="1">Intensified Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2ba9536g5074gca5dg3989g51fc874f548e" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcab75b1fgbde3gcff3g0b4fg03a2bfebe7e5" version="1">Intensified Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd2c5dbegbbb3g12c8ge41cge404fc64db94" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h144c571dg98a5g6625g4ac7g413041c835ba" version="1">Intensified Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h033747b7g5c0fg16b2g13e6g3d61fde453e4" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="he38ed122g9afdgbff3gf566gb3273249b404" version="1">Intensified Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d84efa9g9d45g75fdgcbb3g5b384c9c5083" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8674b07ag201fg4addg6b37g5f1cd1893451" version="1">Intensified Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ca6cc4fg0d0eg614dg91e8g533967486f7f" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0ef536agd1f7g54e3g7e61gcee9996a383a" version="1">Intensified Bell (Debuff)</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6293187g3bcbg4398gde15g7b33073d5af5" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h70ecdc1eg994fg7f5eg0d19g1cbccd884da8" version="1">Intensified Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="hab31e938gde9fg0ed6g2241gd682e8826b91" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
</contentList>